tecommandpost.com 2019-07-11

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                 PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the
Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the
Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete
confidence.
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to
privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects
information from all end users of our Internet services (the "Services")-those who
access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those
who may purchase Products -what we do with the information we collect, and the
choices Visitors have concerning the collection and use of such information. We
request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Personal Information Our Company Collects and How It Is Used
Introduction. Our company collects information in different ways from Visitors
who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites
accessible through our Service.
Registration: Members may be asked to provide certain personal information
when they sign up for our Products or Services including name, address,
telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the
type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal
information collected from Members during the registration process is used to
manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information
may be shared with third parties, as stated herein, or in special circumstances.
However, in instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our
Services, we may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the
name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a
result of the joint promotion for the purpose of offering you other products and
services.

In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any
other purpose. We may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from
personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total
number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we
may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements
that appear on the Services.
Also, with purchases, we supply our member's contact information, to our
business partners, who then may contact the member by telephone after the
member purchase. Sales proceeds are collected by the that business partner
company. We also may supply other companies with contact information, for mail
offers we believe would be of interest to our members, with or without
compensation from those companies. At times we may send an advertisement for
a third party product, where we collect the sales proceeds, and forward the
purchaser's information to that third party.
Our Company Partners and Sponsors: Some products and services may be offered
to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor
seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Members some of these
products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal
information.
Online Shopping: At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or
register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and
service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information,
such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card
information.
If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent
directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the
recipient, such as the recipient's name, address, and phone number. Our
company has no control over the third parties' use of any personal information
you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so.

If you order services or products directly from our company, we use the personal
information you provide to process that order. We do share this information with
outside parties that we do business with.
Online Advertisements: Our company may display our online advertisements. In
those cases we share information about our Visitors and Members collected
through the registration process as well as through online surveys and
promotions with these advertisers.
Additionally, in some instances, we use this information to deliver tailored
advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture
company tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an
advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the information we have
collected, we may then display or send the advertisement to the intended
audience. Our company does share personal information about its Visitors or
Members with these advertisers or joint venture companies.
Responses to Email Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to
our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we
receive.
Voluntary Customer Surveys: We may periodically conduct both business and
individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these
surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to
improve the types of products and services we offer and how we provide them to
you.
We may take the information we receive from individuals responding to our
Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other
customers we may have, to create broader, generic responses to the survey
questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment,
industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated
information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new
services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information
may be shared with third parties.

Promotions: Our company may offer polls, contests, sweepstakes, drawings,
games, content, or other promotions that are sponsored by or cobranded with
third parties. You may be entered in a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion,
simply by making a purchase from us or by providing us with personally
identifiable information for some other reason or purpose. Due to these third
party relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable
information that visitors voluntarily submit to our company. Our company has no
control over third parties' use of this information.
Additionally, personally identifiable information may be collected when you order
products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe
to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our
online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information
that may be collected at these pages include but may not be limited to: name,
address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information,
and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs,
and services. Our sponsors or third parties may send you material that relates to
our company's services, products or activities.
Special Cases: It is our company's policy to use or share the personal information
about Visitors or Members in ways described herein without additional notice or
means to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Also, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or
information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through
our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is
reasonable to do so, including: credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant
database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic
Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or
governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that
is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may
be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user policies;
to operate the Services properly; or to protect our company and our Members.

Notice of Compliance to California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights
Under The California Online Privacy Protection Act and the California Business and
Professions Code
This privacy policy identifies the categories of personally identifiable information
that our company collects through our Web site or online service, about
individual consumers who use or visit our company's commercial Web site or
online service and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom our
company may share that personally identifiable information.
Our company does not maintain a process for an individual consumer who uses or
visits our commercial Web site or online service to review and request changes to
any of his or her personally identifiable information that is collected through our
Web site or online service.
See the section below entitled "Revisions To This Policy" for a description of the
process by which our company notifies consumers who use or visit our
commercial Web site or online service of material changes to our company's
privacy policy for this Web site or online service.
The effective date of this privacy policy is listed at the end of this privacy policy
under the heading, "Last updated."
For the purposes of this policy and California compliance the following definitions
apply:
Depending on the visitor's activity, in our commercial Web site or online service,
the following "personally identifiable information" may be collected, in addition
to information set forth in other sections of this document.
The term "personally identifiable information" means individually identifiable
information about an individual consumer collected online by our company from
an individual and maintained
by our company in an accessible form, and may include any of the following:
(1) A first and last name.

(2) A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or
town.
(3) An e-mail address.
(4) A telephone number.
(5) A social security number.
(6) Any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific
individual.
(7) Information concerning a user that the Web site or online service collects
online, from the user, and maintains in personally identifiable form, in
combination with an identifier described within this privacy policy.
Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a
year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information
about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous
calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared.
To make such a request, please send an email to Privacy@PrivacyRequest.com
and please include the phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, the
domain name of the Web site you are inquiring about, along with your name,
address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving
such a request.
"Cookies" and How Our Company Uses Them. A "cookie" is a small data file that
can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Our company
may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for purposes
stated herein as well as for statistical purposes to improve the products and
services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks.
Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use
of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected
through them.

Our Company Commitment to Children's Privacy. Protecting children's privacy is
especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online
Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore we restrict
our Web site to persons eighteen years or older.
YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU
ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS
WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS
WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE
CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED
AS DOING SO.
Public Forums: Please remember that any information you may disclose in any
Member Directory, or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet,
becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to
disclose personal information in these public areas.
Our Company's Commitment to Data Security: Services and Web sites we sponsor
have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the
information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity
and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security
measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this
information.
Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy: If you have any questions
about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us
through the contact information provided on this Web site.
Revisions to This Policy: Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or
modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and our other policies and
agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting. Your use of
this site after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement
and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement prior to
every use for any changes.
